[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these facts refers to gold in its metallic form?", "correct_answer": "It is the most malleable of all metals", "incorrect_answers": ["It is not a good conductor of electricity", "All of these", "I is a good insulator of heat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A great dog-hater, this villain ranked # 39 on AFI\u2019s list of the 50 top villains, is one of the three from the list coming from an animated film.", "correct_answer": "Cruella De Vil", "incorrect_answers": ["The Queen", "The Wicked Witch of the West", "Mrs. Danvers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pterodactyls were large flying dinosaurs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When used by editors in the film industry, the acronym E.D.L. stands for what?", "correct_answer": "Edit Decision List", "incorrect_answers": ["Editing Dissolve Log", "Editors Dialogue List", "Editors Duplicate Log"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A tabby is a type of domesticated cat with tiger-like stripes and silky fur. Where does the word tabby come from?", "correct_answer": "A suburb of Baghdad", "incorrect_answers": ["A corruption of Tabitha, a name long associated with cats and the devil", "A district of a city in China", "A corruption of its Latin name"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Shreks sidekick in the films Shrek, Shrek 2, and Shrek the Third?", "correct_answer": "Donkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Puss in Boots", "The Frog King", "Fairy Godmother"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Arquette sibling starred in the 1985 movie Desperately Seeking Susan?", "correct_answer": "Rosanna", "incorrect_answers": ["Patricia", "David", "Alexis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bacteria consist of this number of cells.", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["Billions", "3", "Millions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johnny starred in the movie Indian Paint.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Back to the Future, Lous Cafe (from 1955) turns out to be an aerobics center in 1985.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who created the first billion dollar company?", "correct_answer": "J.P. Morgan", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Carnegie", "Alexander Farkas", "Samuel Walton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedy, directed by John Landis, contains the line I know each one of you, like I know my own smell!", "correct_answer": "\u00a1Three Amigos!", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Shop of Horrors", "The Money Pit", "Ferries Buellers Day Off"]}]